Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. Today
we're doing an absolute Ben & Jerry's
classic fish food. Let me show you how
to make it. Chocolate protein shake,
cocoa powder, sweetener, zantham gum,
salt. Blend that all up and throw it in
the freezer for at least 16 hours. And
then once it's nice and frozen, you take
it out and run it under hot water for
about a minute. And then spin it in your
creamy on the light ice cream setting.
It might come out very powdery like mine
did. And if so, just scrape down the
sides and then run it on the respin
setting. Now, if you don't know what the
fish food flavor is from Ben & Jerry's,
it is a chocolate ice cream with
marshmallow swirl, caramel swirl, and
these fudge fish. Instead of those fudge
fish, we are using the best protein
chocolate on the market, the Horbulls
Schwarmles. This tastes exactly like a
crunch bar. So, we're using about half
of that and then running this on the
mixin setting. And it's going to add the
perfect crunch to contrast that rich
chocolatey ice cream. Need something
crunchy in every ice cream. And then
we're topping it with some marshmallows
and then some caramel sauce. Now, let me
know which Ben & Jerry's flavor I should
recreate next. I'll do the most like
comment.